<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.kcachegrind.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kcachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKCachegrindxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">KCachegrind</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">KCachegrind</name>
  <summary>Profiler Frontend</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Frontal de l'analitzador de rendiment</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Frontal de l'analitzador de rendiment</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Rozhraní pro profilaci</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Profiler-Oberfläche</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Profiler Frontend</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Profiler Frontend</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Interfaz de analizador de rendimiento</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Profileerimise kasutajaliides</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Profilatzailearen interfazea</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Profilointikäyttöliittymä</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Interface de profilage</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Interface de analizador de rendemento</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Fronte de profilator</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Frontend Pemprofil</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Interfaccia per la profilatura</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">პროფაილერის წინაბოლო</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">프로파일러 프론트엔드</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Profiler-hulpprogramma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Grensesnitt for profilvising</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Nakładka programu profilującego</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Interface de Análise de Performance</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Interface de análise de performance</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Интерфейс профилировщика</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Rozhranie pre profiláciu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Začelje profila izvajanja</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Profileringsgränssnitt</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Profil Ön Yüzü</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Інтерфейс до Profiler</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxProfiler Frontendxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">分析器前端</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">分析器前端</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      KCachegrind is a profile data visualization tool, used to determine the most time consuming parts in the execution of a program.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KCachegrind és una eina de visualització per a les dades d'anàlisi del rendiment, usada per a determinar les parts que consumeixen més temps en l'execució d'un programa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">KCachegrind és una eina de visualització per a les dades d'anàlisi del rendiment, utilitzada per a determinar les parts que consumixen més temps en l'execució d'un programa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">KCachegrind ist ein Werkzeug zur Visualisierung von Profildaten, um festzustellen, welche Teile bei der Ausführung eines Programms am meisten Zeit brauchen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KCachegrind is a profile data visualisation tool, used to determine the most time consuming parts in the execution of a program.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">KCachegrind estas profildatuma bildigilo, uzata por determini la plej temporabajn partojn en la plenumo de programo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KCachegrind es una herramienta de visualización de datos de análisis de rendimiento que se usa para determinar las partes de un programa que consumen más tiempo durante su ejecución.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">KCachegrind on profileerimisandmete visualiseerimise tööriist, mis võimaldab määrata kindlaks, millised programmi osad nõuavad täitmisel kõige enam aega.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">«KCachegrind», profil datuak irudikatzeko tresna bat da, programa baten exekuzioan denbora gehien behar duten atalak zehazteko erabilia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">KCachegrind on profiilitiedon visualisointityökalu, joka on tarkoitettu helpottamaan ohjelman suorituksen aikaa vievimpien osien tunnistamisessa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KCachegrind est un outil d'affichage des données de profilage, utilisé pour déterminer les segments prenant le plus de temps lors de l'exécution d'un programme.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">KCachegrind é unha ferramenta de visualización de datos de rendemento que se usa para determinar as partes da execución dun programa que consumen máis tempo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Kcachegrind es un instrumento de visualisation de datos de profilo, usate per determinar le partes que consuma le  majoritate de tempore in le execution de un programma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">KCachegrind adalah sebuah alat virtualidasi data profil, digunakan untuk menentukan seberapa memakan waktu dalam pengeksekusian program.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KCachegrind è uno strumento di visualizzazione dei dati di profilatura, usato per determinare dove viene maggiormente speso il tempo durante l'esecuzione di un programma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">KCachegrind პროფილის მონაცემების ვიზუალიზაციის პროგრამაა, რომელიც პროგრამის შესრულების იმ ადგილების დადგენისთვის გამოიყენება, რომლებიც ყველაზე მეტ დროს ხარჯავენ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">KCachegrind는 프로그램을 프로파일링하여 실행 시간의 가장 많은 부분을 차지하는 항목을 찾습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KCachegrind is een hulpmiddel voor visualisatie van profielgegevens en wordt gebruikt om de meest tijdrovende delen in het uitvoeren van een programma te bepalen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KCachegrind jest narzędziem obrazującym dane przy profilowaniu. Jego przeznaczeniem jest wskazanie najbardziej czasochłonnych części programu przy jego wykonywaniu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KCachegrind é uma ferramenta de visualização de dados de performance, usado para determinar as partes que consomem mais tempo na execução de um programa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">KCachegrind é uma ferramenta de visualização de dados de performance, usada para determinar as partes que consomem mais tempo na execução de um programa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">KCachegrind — это средство визуализации данных профилирования, используемое для определения наиболее трудоёмких частей при выполнении программы.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KCachegrind je nástroj na vizualizáciu údajov profilu používaný na určenie časovo najnáročnejších častí v behu programu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">KCachegrind je orodje za vizualizacijo podatkov o profilu, ki se uporablja za določanje najbolj zamudnih delov pri izvajanju programa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kcachegrind; är ett visualiseringsverktyg för profileringsdata, använt för att ta reda på delarna med störst tidsåtgång vid körning av ett program.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">KCachegrind, bir programın yürütülmesinde en çok zaman harcayan parçaları belirlemek için kullanılan bir profil veri görselleştirme aracıdır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KCachegrind — інструмент для показу даних профілювання. Ним можна скористатися для визначення частин програми, які найбільше навантажують систему.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKCachegrind is a profile data visualization tool, used to determine the most time consuming parts in the execution of a program.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">KCachegrind 是一个性能数据可视化工具。它被用于确定程序执行过程中最花时间的部分。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">KCachegrind 是一個配置檔案可視化工具，用於確定執行程序中最耗時的部分。</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ast">Funciones:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Funktionen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Χαρακτηριστικά:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Trajtoj:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Funciones:</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Omadused:</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Ezaugarriak:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Ominaisuuksia:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Characteristicas:</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Fitur:</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Funzionalità:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">თვისებები:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">기능:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Kenmerken:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Funksjonar:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Możliwości:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Recursos:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Возможности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Zmožnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Özellikler:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">功能：</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>KCachegrind visualizes profiles (i.e. runtime characteristics) of applications in various ways,
          including call graph vizualisations and source/disassembler annotation.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">El KCachegrind visualitza les anàlisis del rendiment (és a dir, característiques en temps d'execució) de les aplicacions en diverses maneres, incloent-hi les visualitzacions de les gràfiques de crides i anotacions del codi font/desassemblador.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">KCachegrind visualitza les anàlisis del rendiment (és a dir, característiques en temps d'execució) de les aplicacions en diverses maneres, incloent-hi les visualitzacions de les gràfiques de crides i anotacions del codi font/desassemblador.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">KCachegrind visualisiert Profile (d.h. Laufzeitmerkmale) von Anwendungen auf verschiedene Art und Weise, einschließlich der Visualisierung von Aufrufdiagrammen und von Quelltext- und Disassembler-Anmerkungen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">KCachegrind visualises profiles (i.e. runtime characteristics) of applications in various ways, including call graph visualisations and source/disassembler annotation.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">KCachegrind bildigas profilojn (t.e. rultempajn karakterizaĵojn) de aplikoj laŭ diversaj manieroj, inkluzive de vokografeaj bildigoj kaj fonta/malasemblila komentario.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">KCachegrind visualiza análisis de rendimiento (es decir, características en tiempo de ejecución) de las aplicaciones de diversos modos, incluyendo visualizaciones de gráficos de llamadas y anotaciones de código fuente/desensamblador.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">KCachegrind võib profiile (st käitusaja karakteristika) visualiseerida mitmel moel, kaasa arvatud väljakutsete graafikuna ja lähtekoodi/disassembleri annotatsioonina.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">«KCachegrind»ek aplikazioen profilak (hots, exekuzio aldiko ezaugarriak) hainbat eratan irudikatzen ditu, deien irudikapen grafikoak eta sorburu/desmihiztatzaile idatzoharrak barne.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">KCachegrind visualisoi sovellusprofiileja (esim. ajonaikaisominaisuuksia) monin tavoin kuten kutsukaaviovisualisoinnein ja lähde/disassembler-merkinnöin.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">KCachegrind permet d'afficher les caractéristiques d'exécution (le profilage) d'applications de nombreuses manières, notamment en affichant le graphe d'appels et les annotations des sources et du désassembleur.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Varios tipos de visualizacións dos datos de rendemento dunha aplicación, como un gráfico de chamadas ou anotacións no código fonte ou no código máquina.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">KCachegrind visualisa profilos (.e. characteristicas in tempore de execution) de applicationes in varie modos, includente visualisationes graphich de appello e annotation de fonte/disassemblator.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">KCachegrind memvisualkan profil (mis. karakteristik runtime) pada aplikasi dalam beberapa cara, termasuk visualisasi grafik panggilan dan anotasi sumber/disassembler.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">KCachegrind visualizza profili (cioè caratteristiche a tempo di esecuzione) delle applicazioni in vari modi, tra cui la visualizzazione del grafico delle chiamata e le annotazioni sul sorgente/dal disassemblatore.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">KCachegrind აპლიკაციების პროფილების (გაშვების დროის მახასიათებლების) ვიზუალიზაციას სხვადასხვანაირად ახდენს, გამოძახებების გრაფიკის ვიზუალიზაციის და წყარის/დიზასამბლერის ანოტაციების ჩათვლით.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">KCachegrind는 호출 그래프 시각화, 소스 코드/어셈블리 코드 표시 등 앱 프로필을 다양하게 시각화합니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">KCachegrind visualiseert profielen (d.w.z. karakteristieken tijdens uitvoeren) van toepassingen op verschillende manieren, inclusief visualisaties van aanroepgrafieken en bron/disassembler annotaties.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">KCachegrind obrazuje profile (tj. charakterystyki uruchomieniowe) aplikacji na różne sposoby, także poprzez obrazowanie grafów wywołań i przypisów do kodu/disassemblera.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">O KCachegrind visualiza os dados de performance (características em execução) das aplicações de diversas formas, incluindo visualizações dos grafos de chamadas e a anotação da descodificação para código/Assembly.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">O KCachegrind visualiza os dados de performance (características em tempo de execução) dos aplicativos de diversas formas, incluindo visualizações dos grafos de chamadas e a anotação da descodificação para código-fonte/Assembly.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Визуализация профилей (параметров выполнения) приложений различными способами, включая визуализацию графа вызовов и аннотацию исходного кода и кода дизассемблера.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">KCachegrind vizualizuje profily (teda behovú charakteristiku) aplikácií rôznymi spôsobmi, vrátane vizualizácií grafov volaní a anotácií zdrojov/disassemblera.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">KCachegrind vizualizira profile (tj. značilnosti izvajanja) aplikacij na različne načine, vključno z vizualizacijo grafov klicev in pripisom virov programske kode.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Kcachegrind åskådliggör profiler (dvs, körtidskarakteristik) för program på olika sätt, inklusive åskådliggörande av anropsdiagram och annotering med källkod och disassembler.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">KCachegrind, başvuruların profillerini (diğer bir deyişle, çalışma zamanı özelliklerini) çeşitli şekillerde, çağrı grafiklerinin hazırlanması ve kaynak/ayrıştırıcı açıklaması dahil olmak üzere görselleştirir.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">KCachegrind візуалізує профілі (тобто динамічні характеристики роботи програми) програм у декілька способів, зокрема може показувати граф викликів та анотацію початкового або асемблерного коду.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxKCachegrind visualizes profiles (i.e. runtime characteristics) of applications in various ways, including call graph vizualisations and source/disassembler annotation.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">KCachegrind 将性能数据 (也就是运行时的表现) 以各种方式可视化，包括调用图可视化，以及以源代码/反汇编结果注释。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">KCachegrind 使用各種方式可視化程式的配置檔案（例如：執行庫特點），包含使用圖行可視化和來源 / 反彙編註釋。</li>
      <li>It can load profiles generated by the cache simulation/call tracer Calltree, a Valgrind tool.
          Thus, profiling does not need any preparation, can cope with shared libraries and plugin architectures, and does not influence the measuring itself.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Pot carregar anàlisis de rendiment generades pel traçador de simulacions/crides de la memòria cau Calltree, una eina del Valgrind. Així, l'anàlisi de rendiment no necessita cap preparació, pot funcionar amb biblioteques compartides i arquitectures de connectors, i no té influència sobre la mesura mateixa.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Pot carregar anàlisis de rendiment generades pel traçador de simulacions/crides de la memòria cau Calltree, una eina de Valgrind. Així, l'anàlisi de rendiment no necessita cap preparació, pot funcionar amb biblioteques compartides i arquitectures de connectors, i no té influència sobre la mesura mateixa.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Es kann Profile laden, die von der Cachesimulation/Call Tracer Calltree (ein Valgrind-Werkzeug) generiert wurden. So braucht die Profilierung keine Vorbereitung, ist in der Lage mit gemeinsam verwendeten Bibliotheken und Modul-Architekturen umzugehen und beeinflusst die Messung selbst nicht.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">It can load profiles generated by the cache simulation/call tracer Calltree, a Valgrind tool. Thus, profiling does not need any preparation, can cope with shared libraries and plugin architectures, and does not influence the measuring itself.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Ĝi povas ŝarĝi profilojn generitajn de la kaŝmemorsimulado/voka spurilo Calltree, ilo de Valgrind. Tiel, profilado ne bezonas ajnan preparon, povas trakti komunajn bibliotekojn kaj kromarkitekturojn, kaj ne influas la mezuradon mem.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Puede cargar análisis de rendimiento generados por el trazador de simulación de cache/llamadas Calltree, una herramienta de Valgrind. De este modo, el análisis no necesita ninguna preparación, puede manejar bibliotecas compartidas y arquitecturas de complementos, además de no influir en la propia medida.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Rakendus võib laadida profiile, mis on loodud Valgrindi puhvri matkimise ja väljakutsete jälitajaga CAlltree. Sel moel ei vaja profileerimine mingeid ettevalmistusi, tuleb toime jagatud teekide ja pluginate arhitektuuriga ega mõjuta mõõtmist ennast.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">«Calltree», «Valgrind»eko cache simulazio/dei aztarnari tresnak sortutako profilak zama ditzake. Hortaz, profilatzeak ez du prestaketarik behar, liburutegi partekatuekin eta plugin arkitekturekin moldatzen da, eta ez dio neurketari berari eragiten.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Se osaa ladata välimuistisimulointi- ja kutsujäljitin Calltree (Valgrind-työkalu) tuottamia profiileja, joten profilointi ei vaadi valmistelua, jaetut kirjastot ja liitännäisarkkitehtuurit riittävät, eikä profilointi vaikuta mittaustuloksiin.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Il est capable de charger les fichiers de profilage générés par l'outil de simulation de cache et de traçage des appels Calltree faisant partie de Valgrind. Le profilage ne demande aucune préparation, il gère les bibliothèques partagées et les architectures de modules externes et n'a pas d'effets de bords sur la mesure.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Compatibilidade con datos de rendemento xerados por Calltree, unha ferramenta de Valgrind para a simulación da caché e o seguimento de chamadas. Así a xeración dos datos de rendemento non require de ningún tipo de preparación, as bibliotecas compartidas e as arquitecturas de complementos non resultan un problema, e a xeración dos datos de rendemento non ten ningún impacto nos datos xerados.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Il pote cargar profilos generate per le traciator de simulation/appello Calltree, un instrumento de Valgrind.  Assi, profilar non necessita ulle preparation, pote complir con bibliothecas compartite e architecturas de plugin, e non influentia le mesme misurar.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Ini bisa memuat profil yang dihasilkan oleh simulasi/panggilan pelacak cache Calltree, alat Valgrind. Dengan demikian, pemprofilan tidak perlu persiapan apa pun, bisa mengatasi pustaka yang di-share dan arsitektur plugin, dan tidaklah mempengaruhi pengukuran itu sendiri.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Può caricare profili generati dal simulatore di cache/tracciatore di chiamate Calltree, uno strumento di Valgrind. In questo modo la profilatura non ha bisogno di alcuna preparazione, può gestire le librerie condivise e le architetture con estensioni, e non influenza la misurazione stessa.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">მას შეუძლია ჩატვირთოს პროფილები , რომლებიც კეშის სტიმულატორის/გამოძახებების ტრესერის, Calltree-ის მიერ, ამიტომ, პროფილირებას არანაირი მომზადება არ სჭირება, შეუძლია თავი გაართვას დამატებებსა და გაზიარებულ ბიბლიოთეკებს და თვითონ არაფერს ზომავს.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">Valgrind 도구인 캐시 시뮬레이션/호출 추적기 Calltree의 프로필을 불러올 수 있습니다. 프로파일링 시 별도의 준비 과정이 필요하지 않으며, 공유 라이브러리 및 플러그인으로도 사용할 수 있으며, 측정에 영향을 주지 않습니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Het kan profielen laden gegenereerd door Calltree, de cache simulator/aanroepvolger, een Valgrind hulpmiddel. Profilering heeft geen enkele voorbereiding nodig, kan overweg met gedeelde bibliotheken en plug-in architecturen en heeft geen invloed op de meting zelf.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Może wczytywać profile utworzone przez program śledzący pamięć podręczną symulacji/wywołań Calltree (narzędzie Valgrinda). Dzięki temu profilowanie nie wymaga żadnego przygotowania, działa z współdzielonymi bibliotekami i architekturami wtyczkami, nie wpływając przez to na same pomiary.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Poderá carregar dados de análise gerados pelo sistema de registo/simulação da 'cache' Calltree, uma ferramenta do Valgrind. Como tal, a análise de performance não necessita de nenhuma preparação, poderá lidar bem com bibliotecas dinâmicas e arquitecturas de 'plugins', não influenciado a medição em si.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Ele pode carregar os dados de análise gerados pelo sistema de registro/simulação do cache Calltree, uma ferramenta do Valgrind. Assim, a análise de performance não necessita de nenhuma preparação, poderá lidar bem com bibliotecas dinâmicas e arquiteturas de plugins, e não influencia a própria medição.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Загрузка профилей, созданных программой симуляции кэша/трассировщиком вызовов Calltree (инструментом Valgrind). Таким образом, профилирование не нуждается в какой-либо подготовке, допускает работу с общими библиотеками и архитектурами модулей и не влияет на сам процесс измерения.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Môže načítať profily generované simuláciou cache/trasovaním volaní Caltree, nástrojom Valgrind. Teda, profilovanie nepotrebuje žiadnu prípravu, dá s zvládnuť so štandardnými knižnicami a architektúrami pluginov a neovplyvňuje samotné meranie.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Naloži lahko profile, ustvarjene z simulacijo predpomnilnika/sledilnikom klicev Calltree, orodjem Valgrind. Tako profiliranje ne potrebuje nobene priprave, lahko ga uporabimo s skupnimi knjižnicami in arhitekturami vtičnikov, kar ne vpliva na samo merjenje.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Det kan läsa in profiler skapade av cachesimulatorn och anropsspåraren Calltree, ett Valgrind-verktyg. Sålunda behöver inte profilering någon förberedelse, kan hantera delade bibliotek och arkitekturer med insticksprogram, och påverkar inte själva mätningen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Valgrind aracı olan önbellek simülasyonu/çağrı izleyici Calltree tarafından oluşturulan profilleri yükleyebilir. Dolayısıyla, profil oluşturma herhangi bir hazırlık gerektirmez, paylaşılan kitaplıklar ve eklenti mimarileri ile başa çıkabilir ve ölçümün kendisini etkilemez.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Програма може завантажувати профілі, створені імітатором кешу та засобом трасування викликів Calltree, інструментом Valgrind. Таким чином, профілювання не потребує приготування, може бути виконане із різними спільними бібліотеками та архітектурами додатків, а також не змінюється у результаті виконання процесів вимірювання параметрів роботи.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxIt can load profiles generated by the cache simulation/call tracer Calltree, a Valgrind tool. Thus, profiling does not need any preparation, can cope with shared libraries and plugin architectures, and does not influence the measuring itself.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">它可以加载缓存模拟器/调用追踪器 Calltree (一个 Valgrind 的工具) 生成的性能数据。通过这个方法，性能数据不需要做预先准备，可以处理共享库和插件架构，还不会影响测量本身。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">它可以載入生成自快取模擬 / call tracer Calltree 配置檔案，一個 Valgrind 工具。 因此，分析不需要任何的準備，可以應付函式庫和附加元件架構，並沒有影響測量自己。</li>
      <li>Converter scripts for OProfile, Perl, and PHP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Convertidor de scripts de l'OProfile, Perl i PHP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Convertidor de scripts d'OProfile, Perl i PHP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Konvertierungs-Skripte für OProfile, Perl und PHP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Converter scripts for OProfile, Perl, and PHP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Konvertilaj skriptoj por OProfile, Perl kaj PHP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Scripts de conversión para OProfile, Perl y PHP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Teisendusskriptid OProfile, Perli ja PHP tarbeks.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">OProfile, Perl, eta PHP bihurtzeko gidoiak.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Muunnosskriptit OProfileen, Perliin ja PHP:hen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Scripts de conversion pour « OProfile », « Perl » et « PHP »</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Guións de conversión para OProfile, Perl e PHP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Scripts de Convertitor  per OProfile, Perl, e PHP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Skrip pengkonversi untuk OProfile, Perl, dan PHP</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Script di conversione per OProfile, Perl e PHP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">გადამყვანი სკრიპტები Oprofile-სთვის, Perl-სთვის და PHP-სთვის.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">OPropile, Perl, PHP 변환 스크립트.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Conversiescripts voor OProfile, Perl en PHP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Konverteringsskript for OProfile, Perl og PHP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Przekształcanie skryptów dla OProfile, Perl oraz PHP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Programas de conversão para o OProfile, Perl e PHP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Converta scripts para OProfile, Perl e PHP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Сценарии преобразователя для OProfile, Perl и PHP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Skripty konvertera pre OProfile, Perl a PHP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Skripta pretvornika za OProfile, Perl in PHP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Konverterar skript för OProfile, Perl och PHP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">OProfile, Perl ve PHP için dönüştürücü komut dosyaları.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Скрипти перетворення для OProfile, Perl та PHP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxConverter scripts for OProfile, Perl, and PHP.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">用于 OProfile, Perl 和 PHP 的转换脚本。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">OProfile、Perl 和 PHP 的轉換指令</li>
      <li>Switching between multiple visualization layouts.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Commutació entre múltiples disposicions de visualització.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Commutació entre múltiples disposicions de visualització.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Wechseln zwischen mehreren Visualisierungs-Layouts.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Switching between multiple visualisation layouts.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Ŝanĝi inter pluraj bildigaj aranĝoj.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Intercambio entre distintos esquemas de visualización.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Lülitumine erinevate visualiseerimisvõimaluste vahel.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Irudikapen antolaera anizkoitzen artean aldatzea.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Vaihto useampien visualisointiasettelujen välillä.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Basculer entre plusieurs dispositions d'affichage</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Posibilidade de cambiar a calquera das varias disposicións de visualización.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Commutar inter dispositiones de visualisation multiple.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Peralihan antara tataletak multi visualisasi</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Passaggio tra differenti modalità di visualizzazione.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">გადართვა მრავალ ვიზუალიზაციის განლაგებების შორის.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">여러 시각화 레이아웃 변경.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Schakelen tussen meerdere visualisatie indelingen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Byt mellom ulike visualiseringar.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Przełaczanie pomiędzy wieloma układami obrazowania.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Mudança entre vários formatos de visualização.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Alterne entre múltiplos layouts de visualização.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Переключение между несколькими форматами визуализации.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Prepínanie medzi viacerými rozloženiami vizualizácie.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Preklapljanje med več postavitvami vizualizacije.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Byter mellan flera visualiseringslayouter.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Birden çok görselleştirme düzenleri arasında geçiş yapma.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Можливість перемикання між декількома режимами візуалізації.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSwitching between multiple visualization layouts.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">在多种不同的可视化布局之间切换。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">切換於多個可視化版面。</li>
      <li>Call graph can be exported as image (PNG).</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">La gràfica de crides es pot exportar com a imatge (PNG).</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">La gràfica de crides es pot exportar com a imatge (PNG).</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Aufrufgraph kann als Bild im PNG-Format exportiert werden.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Call graph can be exported as image (PNG).</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Voka grafeo povas esti eksportata kiel bildo (PNG).</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">El gráfico de llamadas se puede exportar como imagen (PNG).</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Väljakutsete graafikut saab eksportida pildina (PNG).</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Deien grafikoa irudi gisa esportatu daiteke (PNG).</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Kutsukaavion voi viedä kuvaksi (PNG).</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Le graphe d'appels peut être exporté au format image (PNG).</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">O gráfico de chamadas pode exportarse como imaxe (PNG).</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Graphico de appello (Call Graph) pote esser exportate como imagine (PNG).</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Grafik panggilan bisa diekspor sebagai citra (PNG).</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Il grafico delle chiamate può essere esportato come immagine (PNG).</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">გამოძახების გრაფიკი PNG გამოსახულების სახით შეგიძლიათ, გაიტანოთ.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">호출 그래프를 그림 파일(PNG)로 내보내기.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Aanroepgrafiek kan geëxporteerd worden als afbeelding (PNG).</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Kallgraf kan eksporterast som bilete (PNG-format).</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Graf wywołań można wyeksportować jako obraz (PNG).</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">O grafo de chamadas pode ser exportado como uma imagem (PNG).</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">O grafo de chamadas pode ser exportado como imagem (PNG).</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Экспорт графа вызовов как изображения в формате PNG.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Grafy volaní sa dajú exportovať do obrázku (PNG).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Graf klicev lahko izvozimo kot sliko (PNG).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Anropsdiagram kan exporteras som bild (PNG).</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Arama grafiği, resim (PNG) olarak dışa aktarılabilir.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Можливість експортування графу викликів у форматі зображення (PNG).</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCall graph can be exported as image (PNG).xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">调用图可被导出为一幅图像 (PNG)。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">Call 圖形可以匯出為圖片（PNG）。</li>
      <li>Simultaneous display of 2 event types in Call and Annotation View</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Visualització simultània de 2 tipus d'esdeveniments a la vista de Crides i anotacions</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Visualització simultània de 2 tipus d'esdeveniments en la vista de Crides i anotacions</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Gleichzeitige Anzeige von 2 Ereignisarten in der Aufruf- und Anmerkungsansicht</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Simultaneous display of 2 event types in Call and Annotation View</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Samtempa montrado de 2 eventotipoj en Voka kaj Prinota Vido</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Visualización simultánea de 2 tipos de eventos en la vista de llamada y anotación</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Korraga kahe sündmusetüübi kuvamine väljakutsete ja annotatsioonide vaates</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Dei eta idatzohar  ikuspegietan 2 gertakari aldi berean azaltzea</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Kahden tapahtumatyypin samanaikainen näyttö kutsu- ja merkintänäkymissä</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Affichage simultané de 2 types d'évènements dans les vues Appel et Annotation</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Visualización simultánea de dous tipos de evento nas vistas de chamadas e de anotacións.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Monstrar simultanee de 2 typos de eventos inVista de Appello (Call)  e Annotation</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Displai serempak dari tipe 2 peristiwa dalam Panggilan dan Tampilan Anotasi</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Visualizzazione simultanea di due tipi di eventi nelle viste delle chiamate delle annotazioni</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">2 მოვლენის ტიპის ერთდროული ჩვენება გამოძახებებისა და ანოტაცების ხედში</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">호출 및 자세한 보기에서 이벤트 형식 두 개 같이 표시</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Gelijktijdige tonen van 2 typen gebeurtenissen in Aanroep- en Annotatieweergave</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Równoczesne wyświetlanie 2 rodzajów wydarzenia w widoku wywołań i przypisów</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Apresentação simultânea de 2 tipos de eventos na Área de Chamadas e Anotações</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Apresentação simultânea de 2 tipos de eventos nos modos de exibição Chamadas e Anotações</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Одновременное отображение двух типов событий на панелях вызовов и аннотаций.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Súčasné zobrazenie 2 typov udalostí v pohľade volaní a anotácií</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Hkratni prikaz dveh vrst dogodkov v pogledu klicev in obvestil</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Visar samtidigt två händelsetyper i anrops- och annoteringsvyer.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Çağrı ve Ek Açıklama Görünümünde 2 etkinliğin eşzamanlı görüntülenmesi</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Можливість одночасного показу двох типів подій у режимі перегляду викликів і анотацій.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSimultaneous display of 2 event types in Call and Annotation Viewxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">在调用与注释视图中同时展示2种事件类型</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">在 Call 和註解顯示中同時顯示兩個活動類型</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Profiling data analysis with KCachegrind</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Anàlisi de les dades del rendiment amb el KCachegrind</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Anàlisi de les dades del rendiment amb KCachegrind</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Analýzy dat profilování pomocí KCachegrind</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Visualisierung eine Datenanalyse mit KCachegrind</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Profiling data analysis with KCachegrind</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Analizo de profildatumoj kun KCachegrind</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Análisis de datos de rendimiento con KCachegrind</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">Profileerimisandmete analüüs KCachegrindis</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Datuen analisia «KCachegrind»ekin profilatzea</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Data-analyysin profilointia KCachegrindilla</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Analyse des données de profilage à l'aide de KCachegrind</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Analizando datos de rendemento con KCachegrind</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Analysis de datos de profilar con KCachegrind</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Pemprofilan analisis data dengan KCachegrind</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Analisi dei dati di profiling con KCachegrind</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">პროფილირების მონაცემების ანალიზი KCachegrind-თან ერთად</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">KCachegrind로 프로파일링 데이터 분석</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Analyse van gegevens profileren met KCachegrind</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Analiza danych profilowania z KCachegrind</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Análise dos dados de performance com o KCachegrind</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Análise dos dados de performance com o KCachegrind</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Анализ данных профилирования в KCachegrind</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Analýza profilovaných údajov pomocou KCachegrind</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Analize podatkov profila s KCachegrind</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Analys av profileringsdata med Kcachegrind</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">KCachegrind ile veri analizini profille</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Аналіз даних профілювання за допомогою KCachegrind</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxProfiling data analysis with KCachegrindxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">使用 KCachegrind 分析数据</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">在 KCachegrind 分析資料統計</caption>
      <image>https://kde.org/images/screenshots/kcachegrind.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://kde.org/applications/development/kcachegrind/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kcachegrind</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kcachegrind</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=kcachegrind&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <update_contact>Josef.Weidendorfer_at_gmx.de</update_contact>
  <provides>
    <binary>kcachegrind</binary>
    <id>org.kde.kcachgrind.desktop</id>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="23.08.3" date="2023-11-09"/>
    <release version="23.08.2" date="2023-10-12"/>
    <release version="23.08.1" date="2023-09-14"/>
    <release version="23.08.0" date="2023-08-24"/>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
</component>
